# Mojgan moradi

# Architecture Engineering



📍 Tehran, Iran

™ mojganmoradi707@gmail.com

+989120599588

in linkedin.com/in/mojganmoradi

★ https://mojganmoradi.com

#### **About Me**

graduate of architectural engineering, who is currently working in my own architectural office. Interested in sustainable architecture with more than 10 years of work experience in the fields of interior and exterior architecture, exhibition and furniture design, green roofs and green spaces, urban and neighborhood design, etc. Proficient in relevant software and interested in team work. I believe that all spaces can be beautiful and functional if there are creative ideas behind them.

	Skills
AutoCAD	
Lumion	
V-Ray For 3D Max	
Autodesk 3ds Max	
Corel DRAW	
Adobe Photoshop	
SketchUp	
Revit	
Corona Renderer	
Grasshopper	
Languages	
persian	
English	

IELTS (Planned)

#### **Professional Experience**

#### Founder Ramko Office, Architecture Engineering, Ramko Office

Feb 2016 - present | Tehran, Iran

- Design, construction and supervision of commercial, office, residential and landscape complexes ra
- · projects Designing
- Facade design
- Supervise the construction of the facade
- Landscape design
- Designing villas and residential apartments
- office and commercial buildings Design
- · Roof garden design
- Supervising the construction of green spaces and projects under construction

#### Senior Design Architect, Omranveys company

Nov 2015 - Dec 2016 | Tehran, Iran

- luxury projects Designing
- Facade design
- Supervise the construction of the facade
- Landscape design
- Designing villas and residential apartments
- office and commercial buildings Design
- · Roof garden design
- Supervising the construction of green spaces and projects under construction

#### Senior Design Architect, Darkoobtalaei 🛮

Nov 2014 - Oct 2015 | Tehran, Iran

- Designing international exhibition stands
- · Interior design of office companies
- Designing executive plans
- International exhibition poster and billboard design
- Designing the main plan of the exhibition
- Supervising the construction of the exhibition
- Selection and purchase of materials

#### **Exhibition and interior designer,** Maxdesigngroup

Aug 2013 – Jan 2014 | Tehran, Iran

- Designing international exhibition stands
- · Interior design of office companies
- Designing executive plans
- International exhibition poster and billboard design
- Designing the main plan of the exhibition

## Assistant Designer, Tehran Beautification org

Jul 2011 - Jul 2013 | Tehran, Iran

worked part-time as an assistant designer in this organization. And among my
duties were editing plans, calculating parking, writing workshop and meter
reports, estimating dilapidated neighborhoods, and presenting alternatives for
beautifying and renovating dilapidated neighborhoods in Tehran

#### **Education**

## Master of Architecture - MArch/Architectural Engineering,

Islamic Azad University North Tehran Branch (Grade 4.6/5) 2016 – 2018 | Tehran, Iran

# Bachelor of Architecture - BArch/• Architectural Engineering,

Natural Disasters Research Institute (NDRI) (Grade 4.29/5) 2013 – 2015 | Tehran, Iran

# Associate of Architecture -AArch/Architectural Engineering,

Institute of Applied Science Technology Jahad Daneshgahi (IASTJD) (Grade 4.42/5) 2010 – 2012 | Tehran, Iran